//creating array and passing the number, questions, options and answers
let questions = [
   {
   	numb: 1,
   	question: "How many books are in the Bible in total?",
   	answer: "66",
   	options: [
   	   "48",
   	   "83",
   	   "66",
   	   "59"
   	]
   },
   {
   	numb: 2,
   	question: "The Gospel of Mark begins with?",
   	answer: "Jesus' baptism by John",
   	options: [
   	   "Jesus' baptism by John",
   	   "Jesus' birth",
   	   "John the Baptist's birth",
   	   "Joseph's dream"
   	]
   },
   {
   	numb: 3,
   	question: "Why did Cain kill Abel?",
   	answer: "He was jealous because God preferred Abel's sacrifice",
   	options: [
   	   "He coveted Abel's land",
   	   "For revenge after Abel stole his wife",
   	   "He was jealous because God preferred Abel's sacrifice",
   	   "He wanted Abel's warm an beautiful coat"
   	]
   },
   {
   	numb: 4,
   	question: "What did King David do when he became infatuated with Bathsheba?",
   	answer: "Arranged to have her husband killed, then married her",
   	options: [
   	   "Conquered Jerusalem",
   	   "Sang a song to her while playing the Iyre",
   	   "Committed suicide",
   	   "Arranged to have her husband killed, then married her"
   	]
   },
   {
   	numb: 5,
   	question: "When Moses came down from Mt. Sinai what did he discover the Israelites worshiping?",
   	answer: "A golden calf",
   	options: [
   	   "A statue of Baal",
   	   "A golden calf",
   	   "Himself",
   	   "The sun"
   	]
   },
   {
   	numb: 6,
   	question: "How long did Methuselah live?",
   	answer: "969 years",
   	options: [
   	   "969 years",
   	   "873 years",
   	   "1001 years",
   	   "99 years"
   	]
   },
   {
   	numb: 7,
   	question: "What did King Solomon propose to do when two women were claiming to be a child's real mother?",
   	answer: "Cut the baby in two",
   	options: [
   	   "Cast lots with the loser being stoned to death",
   	   "Give the child to the richer woman",
   	   "Cut the baby in two",
   	   "Take the child for himself"
   	]
   },
   {
   	numb: 8,
   	question: "How did Jesus enter Jerusalem on Palm Sunday?",
   	answer: "On a donkey",
   	options: [
   	   "On his hands and knees",
   	   "On a donkey",
   	   "On foot",
   	   "With a car"
   	]
   },
   {
   	numb: 9,
   	question: "How long did it rain during the deluge that killed everyone except for Noah and his family?",
   	answer: "Forty days and nights",
   	options: [
   	   "Twelve days and nights",
   	   "One day",
   	   "About six months",
   	   "Forty days and nights"
   	]
   },
   {
   	numb: 10,
   	question: "Who or what is an epistle?",
   	answer: "A letter that became a book of the bible",
   	options: [
   	   "A letter that became a book of the bible",
   	   "A crown of thorns",
   	   "A person who spread the word of Jesus",
   	   "A sermon given by Jesus"
   	]
   },
]